<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <title>Miko Ademagic</title>
	<subtitle></subtitle>
	<link href="http://ademagic.com/feed.xml" rel="self"/>
	<link href="http://ademagic.com/"/>
	<updated>2021-08-25T00:00:00Z</updated>
	<id>http://ademagic.com</id>
	<author>
  <name>Miko Ademagic</name>
  <email>miko@ademagic.com</email>
	</author>
	
  
  <entry>
    <title>Release IV: A New Hope</title>
    <link href="http://ademagic.com/posts/release-4-a-new-hope/"/>
    <updated>2021-08-25T00:00:00Z</updated>
    <id>http://ademagic.com/posts/release-4-a-new-hope/</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[
      <p>I was contemplating rebuilding my website on a new platform for a while now. Mainly because I couldn't remember how to drive it, mainly because I forgot how to, mainly because didn't document it for myself. After thinking about it, I realised that those reasons weren't good enough. So here it is, the first release in over a year.</p>
<p>Besides, adapting to legacy systems is my (non-voluntary) jam. It's not impossible. I used to build on legacy tech in my T-16 back home.</p>
<p>What copyright infringement?</p>
<h3>Replacing Commento with Disqus</h3>
<p>I removed <a href="https://commento.io/">Commento</a>. It's a lightweight and minimal embeddable comments widget that you should get behind if you can. It doesn't sell your data, show you ads or any other modern internet stuff. I love it. But, given that it costs $USD, the $AUD wasn't having a good time, and more than anything <em>nobody was using it</em>, I decided to end my subscription. A long time ago. I just didn't remove it til now.</p>
<p>I replaced it with <a href="https://disqus.com">Disqus</a>, and updated the <a href="/credits">Credits</a> page accordingly. I'm looking forward to swapping back one day.</p>
<h3>The usual typography changes</h3>
<p>I replaced my Permanent Marker heading font with a very bold, very italic version of Chivo. I like the big blocky minimalist look of it, hoping it will inspire a redesign. While I was at it, I also replaced Frank Ruhl Libre with Kaisei Tokumin. Honestly, this was just filler work. More changes soon, I hope.</p>
<p>✌️</p>

    ]]></content>
  </entry>
	
  
  <entry>
    <title>Release 3: Back to work</title>
    <link href="http://ademagic.com/posts/release-3-back-to-work/"/>
    <updated>2020-06-01T00:00:00Z</updated>
    <id>http://ademagic.com/posts/release-3-back-to-work/</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[
      <p>Over the past 3 months or so I've had the luxury of spending a good chunk of time on my website. Voluntarily.</p>
<p>I resigned from my role at Finder right before COVID and all the fun that came with it. Since then, I've been hammering away at code pretty hard, both to learn new things and to try and dust off the developer part of my brain. I'm excited to say that starting June 1, I will start my new role as Senior Front End Developer at <a target="_blank" href="https://www.innowell.org">InnoWell</a>.</p>
<p>To commemorate the occasion, I added a bunch of stuff to the site. Some without much forethought. Enjoy.</p>
<h3>About me: A Timeline</h3>
<p>I gave my <a href="/about">About</a> page a little facelift, updated some copy, and in perhaps my cheesiest move, added a timeline of my career. The CSS was fun to build, and figuring out what to put in there was fun too. I'll likely add more animations and interactions to it in future. I also took that opportunity to learn a bit more about Eleventy's <a href="https://www.11ty.dev/docs/data-cascade/">Data Cascade</a>.</p>
<h3>Removing dependency on the Hylia fork</h3>
<p>Not a huge change, but the code's been pushed to a <a href="https://www.github.com/ademagic/site">fresh repo</a> which is no longer a fork (but a clone) of <a href="https://hylia.website">Hylia</a>. I updated the docs to reflect this. Mainly just makes my commit graph look prettier, but semantically makes sense because I'm completely diverging from the repo and not planning to merge back into canonical.</p>
<h3>Socials component reworked</h3>
<p>I use one partial to build the social icons in the footer, and on my about page. The socials data was statically added to the partial, but after learning about the Data Cascade, I realised I had a JSON data file where this stuff was nicely stored. I reworked it to use the social data and made some other minor visual updates to it. Also, I'm not looking for work anymore, so the title's gone.</p>
<h3>Soundtracks!</h3>
<p>I'm a big fan of music while I work, and while I do pretty much anything else. Since most of it's over Spotify, I thought it might be interesting to add a widget to the end of the post. I went and retrospectively added soundtracks to my other posts, too. If you like what I listen to, or think you could recommend something I'd enjoy, hit me up!</p>
<h3>Fancy first letter styles</h3>
<p>Like I said, no forethought. Why not?</p>

    ]]></content>
  </entry>
	
  
  <entry>
    <title>5 Steps To Writing A Good Technical Test</title>
    <link href="http://ademagic.com/posts/tech-tests/"/>
    <updated>2020-05-23T00:00:00Z</updated>
    <id>http://ademagic.com/posts/tech-tests/</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[
      <p>Technical tests are take-home (or in-person) excercises that allow developers to demonstrate their ability and approach. As an interviewee, proving you have the skills for the job can be nerve-racking (I've totally bottomed-out on more than one). As an interviewer it can be hard to ask the right questions, and to get the answer you're looking for.</p>
<p>In the last few weeks of my job hunt, I spent more time completing technical tests than working through my training plan. With that behind me, and with the time I spent assessing technical applicants over the years, I've collated a few tips on how to put together a fair and optimal take-home test for you and your candidates.</p>
<h2>5 steps to writing a good take-home technical test</h2>
<h3>1. Write your criteria</h3>
<p>Create a marking criteria that outlines what you'll be looking for when reviewing the test, complete with weighting/priority. Are you trying to understand their approach to structuring classes? How important is test coverage? How about a bug or feature backlog? Do you want to see design skills? All of these things are valid. It's important that you're thorough and that you write all of this out for yourself.</p>
<p><img src="/images/tech-tests/find-x.jpg" alt="Funny test answer, find x of a right angled triangle, circled here it is" title="The clearer you are, the better the answers you'll get. Sourced from funnytab.net"></p>
<h3>2. Be realistic about your timing</h3>
<p>Things start to get tricky now. Go back over your criteria and figure out how much time you expect people to spend doing this. Typically, the suggested time for a take-home test is 2-3 hours. Any longer, and candidates may not bother with taking the test. However, I have spent &gt;12 hours on a 3 hour test for a job I really wanted (and got), and I'm sure I'm not the only one.</p>
<p>Anything you can provide to help set them up, like substantial dummy data or designs, will go a long way. Breaking up the test into two phases can be helpful too, though that could mean a whole extra step in your interview process.</p>
<p>Keep in mind that your candidates may be taking multiple tests while still tending to work and other responsibilities. Candidates who want to work for you will try to prioritise your test, but understand that you're starting to optimise for the person with the most time instead of the right person.</p>
<h3>3. Do the test yourself</h3>
<p>If you can, complete it yourself according to the timing guidelines, and then rigorously assess using your own criteria. Validate whether you'll get what you're looking for in the time you set aside for it. <a href="https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/MoSCoW_method">MoSCoW</a> your criteria, consider revising it, and if necessary, do the test again.</p>
<p>Maybe get some of your colleagues to do it too. Keep in mind that you're <em>testing the test</em>, it's not a reflection on your or your colleague's abilities. What you're looking for is a test that can be completed, and one that you and your team can confidently (and consistently) review.</p>
<figure>
<img alt="scene from kung fury, hackerman codes away gibberish on retro computer" src="https://media.giphy.com/media/l46C6sdSa5DVSJnLG/giphy.gif"/>
<figcaption>
  Well, interviewer, I'm glad you asked – I'd say my biggest weakness is not being able to pick the right images for blogposts.
</figcaption>
</figure>
<h3>4. Share the criteria with the candidate</h3>
<p>I can't stress this enough. Tell them what you're looking for so they know what to prioritise. If you're asking a full stack developer to write a complex microservice architecture in node that feeds data to a simple app, and then you reject them based on their lack of responsive UI (that you didn't ask for), nobody's gonna have a good time.</p>
<p>This is also the time to share any code styles or preferences that you're looking for. It's a good way to test somebody's adaptability. Just remember – not following the code structure you'd use doesn't necessarily make the candidate a bad fit.</p>
<h3>5. Always give feedback</h3>
<p>Be fair, and be prompt. Let them know (as soon as you can) exactly why they didn't meet your standards, where they fell short and where/how they can improve. The criteria you wrote in step 1 should make this real easy for you. For bonus points, tell them what you liked and what they did well.</p>
<p>Remember, your candidate has put a great deal of time and effort into this process, sometimes prioritising it over other things that are valuable or important to them. Reciprocate with empathy, tact and effort.</p>
<h2>My favourite test I've written</h2>
<p>The best test I ever wrote was actually not a take-home test. It was an in-person pair programming challenge which could be done remotely as well.</p>
<p>I wanted to test for a candidate's ability to adapt to a styleguide or design system, and their approach to consuming and extending existing tooling and components. I wanted to know how the candidate would work with others, usually with engineers they'd never met. I was also looking for knowledge of semantics, accessibility, BEM, OOCSS and Atomic Design.</p>
<p>I created a codepen where I included our whole UI library, and created some UI that adhered to our styleguide. The challenge was to add a new component which would match a design I provided. I acted as an in-person stack overflow, but the candidate was welcome to google whatever they wanted (I even helped, and sometimes had to do it myself).</p>
<p>I could get to my outcome within about 45 minutes. While there were some failed attempts, there were many good ones, and it was obvious when someone was stellar. The successful candidate and I discussed the significance of nesting in our styleguides, she followed (and explained) the <a href="https://csswizardry.com/2012/06/the-open-closed-principle-applied-to-css/">open-closed principle</a>, and I helped her navigate our documentation so she could focus on coding. She didn't complete the test, but that wasn't important.</p>
<h2>Conclusion</h2>
<p>Technical tests suck, but a good testing experience can do so much to grow both your candidate and your team. It's also an opportunity for you to set up a good relationship with the industry, and start a smooth onboarding with your future teammate. As much as you're assessing the candidate, they're also assessing you. Any thought or effort you put into your testing process will be returned tenfold.</p>
<p>I'd love to know what experience you've had with technical tests, or examples of great testing experiences – leave a comment below!</p>
<p>✌️</p>

    ]]></content>
  </entry>
	
  
  <entry>
    <title>Release 2: Mostly Typography Updates</title>
    <link href="http://ademagic.com/posts/release-2-typography-updates/"/>
    <updated>2020-05-11T00:00:00Z</updated>
    <id>http://ademagic.com/posts/release-2-typography-updates/</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[
      <p>If you know me, you know I blame all my hangups in Design on how long it takes me to decide on typography. Here's me having a second (and probably not last) go at improving it.</p>
<h3>Inline Code Blocks Facelift</h3>
<p>You know, the <code>&lt;code/&gt;</code> ones. They already steal enough cognitive attention without also being huge and bold. Now they're the same size as the text, with a little extra breathing room. Also changed some of the colours around to make them a little more subtle.</p>
<h3>Actual Font Weights</h3>
<p>I thought I kept importing bad Google Fonts, when actually I was using the Fonts v1 API syntax with a v2 API request. D'oh, Miko.</p>
<p>For now, I've imported two other weights for the Frank Ruhl Libre font family so that <strong>the strong tags</strong> have some more visual weight. More typography changes to come, I'm sure.</p>
<h3>Credits Page</h3>
<p>I really like <a href="https://dbanks.design" rel="external">Danny Banks</a>'s site, and I thought the idea of the open-source credits page was cool. So I've replaced the Hylia link in the footer with a link to my <a href="/credits">Credits</a> page. Hopefully more things make it on here as I go more crazy than just updating typography.</p>
<p>Next one's the homepage, I swear.</p>
<p>✌️</p>

    ]]></content>
  </entry>
	
  
  <entry>
    <title>Zoom Etiquette</title>
    <link href="http://ademagic.com/posts/zoom-etiquette/"/>
    <updated>2020-04-02T00:00:00Z</updated>
    <id>http://ademagic.com/posts/zoom-etiquette/</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[
      <p><img src="/images/zoom-etiquette/digital_transformation_covid.jpg" alt="Who led the digital transformation of your company? The C.E.O, C.T.O or Covid-19?" title="Be honest. Image from somewhere on twitter, if you know the original source please let me know."></p>
<p>By now you've probably had to use a video conferencing platform like <a href="https://zoom.us" target="_blank">Zoom</a> or <a href="https://hangouts.google.com/" target="_blank">Hangouts</a> to conduct a meeting. A &quot;Brady Bunch&quot; of faces talking at each other, hoping to not talk over their boss, occasionally catching their own reflections/portraits for a bit too long.</p>
<p><img src="/images/zoom-etiquette/The_Brady_Bunch.jpg" alt="The Brady Bunch 3x3 grid of faces, also a typical Zoom meeting" title="Your meeting, probably. Image from the Brady Bunch Wikipedia page."></p>
<p>You may have found this kind of meeting frustrating at times, but try to imagine a group of you were actually in a room together while the rest are in the video chat. The conversations stop including certain people, video chat participants become easy to ignore <em>and</em> can easily ignore you. This can be the reality of working in a distributed team.</p>
<p>It doesn't have to – there are simple things you can do to stay collaborative and inclusive. The main thing to keep in mind is that your distributed video chats need to try and emulate everybody being in the same room as best as possible, and the whole team needs to be aligned to this.</p>
<p>Here's how Design Operations (DOPS) at Finder did it.</p>
<h2>Before the Meeting</h2>
<p>It's helpful to identify some roles and rules as a team. This may not always be possible given you could be meeting with clients, but an awareness of these was very useful for us. We established these roles naturally, but intentionally defining these would help too.</p>
<h3>The Meeting Conductor</h3>
<p>The Conductor makes sure that people are heard, included, and have the chance to participate in discussions. This can be one or more people. This doesn't have to be your leader or manager, but is typically the person who also organised the meeting.</p>
<p>This role exists in in-person meetings as well - they're typically the person who makes sure the meeting stays on track. The difference now is that this person has to be aware of everyone in the video call, and politely make time for them to say something, especially if they've been attempting to.</p>
<p>Just like in in-person meetings, this person should be in charge of either note taking, organising note taking, or any other follow-up work that should come <a href="#heading-after-the-meeting">after the meeting</a>.</p>
<h3>The Loud Voices, The Quiet Voices</h3>
<p>People who are typically loud or talkative in meetings need to be aware of their habits, as they may unintentionally exclude the voices of other members in the team. Similarly, people who are reserved or quiet will often not get <em>or take</em> their chance to talk like their counterparts will. Calling this out (even in private) takes a lot of trust between team members, but we've found the benefits carry to other teams, too.</p>
<p>It's important to note that this is not an exercise to change people's personalities (i.e. get talkative people to shut up, get the reserved people to speak up) – it's an exercise of self awareness to help people judge how they can best contribute to the team.</p>
<blockquote>
<p>&quot;Okay, I think I'm talking too much – sorry Taylor, did you have something to say?&quot;</p>
</blockquote>
<p><em>Kayne East realises he has been The Loud Voice</em></p>
<p>Making ourselves aware of which role we typically play means the Meeting Conductor can do a better job as well.</p>
<h2>During the Meeting</h2>
<p>Given that our meetings were both in person and using tech, there were a series of things we had to keep in mind throughout the meeting to keep it running smoothly.</p>
<h3>Sound Check</h3>
<p>When the meeting starts, you effectively just &quot;ninja&quot; in. The rest of the room may not be aware that you're in the meeting, and that's ok for meetings with more participants, or &quot;listening&quot; meetings. One habit we got into at the beginning of our meetings was to ensure that everyone can actually be heard, either by:</p>
<ol>
<li>Making sure to start with conversation.</li>
<li>Greeting any person who joined, and waiting for an audible response.</li>
<li>If you haven't got an audible response, asking for a quick sound check. This is a little more explicit than just repeating step 2.</li>
</ol>
<h3>Video Feed</h3>
<p>It's very helpful if everyone can join with their video feed. Speaking face to face encourages empathy, and lets the meeting participants read your body language and emotional responses to conversations. However, sometimes participants can't have their video enabled for various reasons. This is ok, too.</p>
<p>Keep in mind that not all video is visible at once. Sometimes it's also necessary to disable video for the benefit of the connection.  Given that video can be unreliable, always remember to communicate first by talking. Only nodding and shaking your head, or gesturing, can be an especially hard habit to get out of.</p>
<h2>After the Meeting</h2>
<p>As in real life, it's still impossible to have a perfectly seamless conversation. It's important that after the meeting, the Meeting Conductor can follow up with the team and make sure that they all get their say in. It's helpful to have meeting notes that you can asynchronously add to, but is also just generally good practice when sharing information with a distributed team. This enables you to record and validate decisions more easily, and avoids creating tribal knowledge through documentation.</p>
<p>In summary, these are just techniques to help you on your way to making the most out of our new Work From Home reality. A meeting is only as effective as the participants are aligned and constructive. Hopefully a joint awareness and some common rules and guidelines to follow helps you achieve that alignment.</p>
<p>I'd like to reiterate a caveat though – these are techniques that worked for DOPS, a team with some distributed members which was also WFH-enabled. Today, we're living in different times. I'll leave you with this tweet for a bit of grounding.</p>
<blockquote class="twitter-tweet"><p lang="en" dir="ltr">&quot;You are not working from home; you are at your home during a crisis trying to work.&quot;<br><br>I&#39;ve heard this twice today. I think it&#39;s an important distinction worth emphasising.</p>&mdash; Neil Webb (@neilmwebb) <a href="https://twitter.com/neilmwebb/status/1245012958415073282?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw">March 31, 2020</a></blockquote> <script async src="https://platform.twitter.com/widgets.js" charset="utf-8"></script> 
<p>What techniques have you found effective for running your video meetings? Leave me a comment below, I'm interested to hear them!</p>
<p>✌️</p>

    ]]></content>
  </entry>
	
  
  <entry>
    <title>Release 1: The First Fixes</title>
    <link href="http://ademagic.com/posts/release-1-the-first-fixes/"/>
    <updated>2020-04-01T00:00:00Z</updated>
    <id>http://ademagic.com/posts/release-1-the-first-fixes/</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[
      <p>That's what I get for not testing my website more thoroughly. But, like I said, MVP. Heck, this isn't even the design I wanted to release with, so that should tell you something.</p>
<p>I'm going to try to make an effort to document all the changes I make to my website as I go. I think I'd find it interesting to go back over these in some distant future, maybe you'll enjoy it too. Of course, I'm going to be continuously deploying changes as I see fit – I'll still try to document these in release posts. You can find them tagged as <a href="/tags/release">release</a>.</p>
<h3>Blue Favicon</h3>
I changed the favicon to blue after seeing it on a non-dark-mode tab... It reminded me of an <a href="https://www.logolynx.com/topic/nestle+purina+petcare" target="_blank">aussie pet food brand</a>'s logo.
<h3>New body typeface</h3>
I previously used Playfair Display, but given that they're intended for large stylistic headings, I shouldn't have. Lots of hairlines on Chrome for Windows were disappearing. For now, I've changed to <a href="https://fonts.google.com/specimen/Frank+Ruhl+Libre">Frank Ruhl Libre</a> Regular.
<h3>New background colour</h3>
I changed the body background from `#f4fdfc` to `#fafffe`. I intentionally wanted a white in a blue shade, but this was uncomfortably blue on non-mac screens. I also swapped around the body and footer background colours on dark mode.
<h3>Header and Footer refresh</h3>
I didn't like how my header looked on mobile, so I moved the theme toggle to the footer and redid the footer a little. I also added my logo to my header. I redid the theme toggle as well – I thought the emojis were cute but seeing the non-apple ones in the button made me change my mind. I reverted the design to something like what it was originally in Hylia, though I plan to revisit the theming completely.
<h3>Next</h3>
The next few deployments should actually contain new features this time. I tried to be cute with keeping the old splash page of my site when moving to this new one, but that one took me all of two hours and now looks messy and doesn't fit the rest of the design. I'll be spending most of my time on updating this, and may do it in a few iterations. Other than that I have a few components I want to create for the blog pages, and will redesign my about page as well.
<p>If you've got any suggestions for me, or see any issues, feel free to comment here or drop me a line on any of my socials.</p>
<p>✌️</p>

    ]]></content>
  </entry>
	
  
  <entry>
    <title>Hello, World! Again!</title>
    <link href="http://ademagic.com/posts/welcome/"/>
    <updated>2020-03-30T00:00:00Z</updated>
    <id>http://ademagic.com/posts/welcome/</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[
      <p>Very original, I know. Especially because this isn't the first iteration of my website and I bet I've probably used this same line before, even in iterations that never saw the light of the internet. If anything, I'm consistent.</p>
<p>I've had another go at getting a site live, and I'll be trying to blog my way through it as I go. While this site was born in the time of COVID-19, I've been at it for a few months longer. Not working on it constantly, though – There's been a break as I was going through some personal challenges, and obviously the odd redesign. As &quot;perfect is the enemy of done&quot;, recently I've decided to really double down on an &quot;MVP&quot;. This is all content for future blogposts though. And so, here we are.</p>
<p>Every time I've done this, the industry has been different and as a result, so's the tech my site's built in. This time 'round, I've decided to go easy and build with:</p>
<ul>
<li><a href="#heading-eleventy">Eleventy</a> as a static site generator</li>
<li><a href="#heading-hylia">Hylia</a> as a starter template for Eleventy</li>
<li><a href="#heading-github-pages">GitHub Pages</a> for hosting</li>
</ul>
<h2>Eleventy</h2>
<p><a href="https://www.11ty.dev/" target="_blank">Eleventy</a> is a simple static site generator. This is definitely the best value prop I've seen and is the only intro text on their site before getting straight into how to use it. It's really that simple, <em>but</em> has so much capability as well. I've always been very pro static sites, especially in the ever-complexifying world of web apps and javascript libraries. Maybe coz I'm slightly bitter, but definitely because I'm a fan of simplicity and keeping things lean for the user.</p>
<p>For what I wanted from my site, I also didn't believe I needed the functionality of a complex CMS or backend. This blogpost is written completely in markdown, and it uses <a href="https://mozilla.github.io/nunjucks/templating.html" target="_blank">Nunjucks</a> for templating, with front matter for page settings. I have to redeploy the entire site every time I create a new blogpost (well, technically I don't if I'd used Netlify – more on that later). That's ok for me though.</p>
<p>I started out with Eleventy, and getting up and running was simple. It became obvious pretty quickly that there was a lot that I could do with Eleventy that I hadn't even considered, or would take me a while to learn or implement. Eleventy recognises that, too – which is why step 3 of their awesome <a href="https://www.11ty.dev/docs/getting-started/" target="_blank">Getting Started</a> documentation is <a href="https://www.11ty.dev/docs/starter/" target="_blank">Starter Projects</a>. Enter Hylia.</p>
<h2>Hylia</h2>
<p><a href="https://hylia.website/" target="_blank">Hylia</a> is a starter project for Eleventy, with Netlify CMS preconfigured. If you've already clicked through to the Starter Projects page, you'll see there's no shortage. My research through them was brief – I didn't look much further than <a href="https://twitter.com/hankchizljaw" target="_blank">Andy Bell</a>'s face, and quickly decided on Hylia. This is because:</p>
<ul>
<li>I follow him on twitter, and know that he puts a focus on semantics, accessibility, and systematic design – so we share a lot of the same values as developers/technologists.</li>
<li>The example site was nice and simple.</li>
<li>I love <a href="https://zelda.fandom.com/wiki/Hylia" target="_blank">Zelda</a>.</li>
</ul>
<p>After forking the repo I was quickly impressed. The site is generated using <a href="https://github.com/design-tokens/community-group" target="_blank">Design Tokens</a>, meaning the core aspects of the design like colours, sizes/spacing, and fonts could be configured at a very elementary level. I was able to start redesigning the blog in minutes.</p>
<p>It also generates a <code>/styleguide/</code> page from your tokens, which lets you get a quick overview of the changes you make – though the <a href="https://github.com/hankchizljaw/hylia/tree/master/src/posts" target="_blank">example posts</a> are also helpful while redesigning. Find out more in the <a href="https://github.com/hankchizljaw/hylia#design-tokens-and-styleguide" target="_blank">README</a>.</p>
<p>It's also got Netlify's CMS preconfigured, which seems to be a strong sell but I didn't consider it. I may well use it eventually, but since I was already working with GitHub Pages, I decided to make things difficult for myself.</p>
<h2>GitHub Pages</h2>
<p>I really like that <a href="https://pages.github.com/" target="_blank">GitHub pages</a> is a thing. Automatically deploying and hosting your github repo's root index file is simple and clever. I've been hosting my site in this way for a few years, mainly because I haven't needed the complexity of my own custom hosting setup and so I also haven't been considering other methods. Now that I've built my site with Eleventy, I'm weighing up my options again.</p>
<p>So, there it is. You've made it this far. Hopefully you found this intro blog useful, and hopefully you'll come back for more later. I've got all sorts of stuff planned – new animations, a nicer About page, heaps of blogposts and projects, probably changing my typography 5 or 6 times... If you've got any feedback for me I'd love some – drop a comment here or <a href="https://twitter.com/miko_a" target="_blank">@ me on twitter</a>.</p>
<p>Stay safe. ✌️</p>

    ]]></content>
  </entry>
	
</feed>
